Evil hides in plain sight
I See You is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Adam Randall.
When a 10-year-old boy goes missing, lead investigator Greg Harper struggles to balance
the pressure of the investigation and troubles with his wife, Jackie.
Facing a recent affair, great strain is put on the family that
slowly gnaws away at Jackie's grip on reality.
But after a malicious presence manifests itself in their home and puts their son, Connor, in mortal
danger, the cold, hard truth about evil in the Harper household is finally uncovered.
Jackie Harper, played by Helen Hunt.
Greg Harper, played by Jon Tenney.
Alec Travers, played by Owen Teague.
Connor Harper, played by Judah Lewis.
Mindy, played by Libe Barer.
Detective Spitzky, played by Gregory Alan Williams.
I See You is a 2019 American crime horror thriller mystery film
directed by Adam Randall from a screenplay by Devon Graye.
It stars Helen Hunt, Jon Tenney, and Judah Lewis.
Its plot follows the sequence of strange events that begin to happen inside an investigator's
family home after the case of a child who disappeared 15 years ago is reopened.
It premiered at the 2019 SXSW Film Festival and was released on
December 6, 2019 to generally positive reviews.
The film explores themes of small town, husband wife
relationship, kidnapping, detective, investigation.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and dark.